Like Diane said, changing the unit of diversion can change the variability of
就像 Diane 所以说的 更改分组单元可能导致指标的差异性发生变化
a metric, sometimes pretty dramatically.
有时候这种变化还很大
I Googled Diane and
我通过在 Google 上搜索了解到
some of her colleagues tested this by measuring the variability of a metric
Diane 和她的同事们曾针对指标差异性的变化开展过一些测试
for two different units of diversion, query and cookie.
他们使用查询和 cookie 这两种分组单元来衡量指标的差异性
Diverting by query is a type of event based diversion, since for
按查询分组是一种基于事件的分组方式
a search engine, a query really is an event.
因为对于搜索引擎而言 查询实际上是一种事件
The metric they measured was called coverage,
他们衡量的指标是覆盖率
which is defined as the percentage of queries for which an ad is shown.
也就是显示广告的查询比例
You can calculate this by taking the total number of queries with an ad and
将显示广告的总查询量除以总查询量
dividing by the total number of queries.
即可计算出这一覆盖率
Since the number of queries is the denominator,
因为查询量是分母
that means that the unit of analysis in this case is a query.
也就是说 在这个例子中 分析单元是查询
So when the unit of diversion was a query, then the unit of diversion and
如果分组单元也是查询
the unit of analysis were the same.
那么分组单元和分析单元即相同
This plot shows the results Diane saw, with the standard error on
这个图表显示了 Diane 看到的结果
the Y-axis and 1 over the square root of the sample size on the X-axis.
其 Y 轴为标准误差 X 轴为样本量的平方根分之一
The red line shows the standard error for cookie-based diversion and
红线显示了基于 cookie 的分组方式的标准误差
the black line shows the standard error for query-based diversion.
黑线显示了基于查询的分组方式的标准误差
To see why the X-axis is 1 over the square root of N,
为什么 X 轴是样本量 N 的平方根分之一？
instead of N directly, recall that the standard error for
为什么它不直接是样本量 N？我们曾介绍过
a binomial is proportional to 1 over the square root of N.
二项式的标准误差与样本量 N 的平方根分之一成比例
That's why both lines here are straight.
所以两条线都是直线
Notice that when the unit of diversion is a cookie,
注意看 这里的分组单元是 cookie
which is not the same as the unit of analysis,
它不同于分析单元
the variability is much higher than when the two units are the same.
所以其差异性比两个单元相同时的情况要高得多
The variability might be higher by as much as four times,
根据样本量
depending on the sample size.
差异性的差异可能高达四倍
The standard error for
基于查询的分组方式的标准误差
the query based diversion was also much closer to the analytical standard error.
也更接近分析标准误差
This lines up with what Diane mentioned earlier, that when your unit of analysis
就像 Diane 之前所提到的
and your unit of diversion are the same, the variability tends to be lower and
如果分析单元和分组单元相同 那么其差异性较两个单元不同的情况更小
closer to the analytical estimate than when they're different.
且更接近分析估计
If you'd like to see more details about these results,
如果想要详细了解这些结果
see the paper linked in the instructor's notes.
请参阅讲师备注中链接的论文
Now for each of the following cases,
对于以下所有案例
would you expect the analytic variance to match the empirical variance?
你认为哪些案例的分析方差会与经验方差一致？
First, suppose your metric is click-through-rate,
第一个 假设你的指标是点击率
defined as the number of clicks divided by the number of page views, and
即点击量除以页面查看量
suppose your unit of diversion is a cookie.
且分组单元是 cookie
Second, suppose your metric is the number of cookies that view your
第二个 假设你的指标是查看主页的 cookie 数量
homepage, which you're computing on a daily basis.
且你根据每日数据进行计算
You're using event based diversion, and in this case, an event is a page view.
你使用基于事件的分组方法 在这个案例中 事件就是页面查看
Third, suppose your metric is the percent of users that sign up for
第三个 假设你的指标是注册辅导服务的用户比例
coaching, that is the total number of users who sign up for
也就是注册了辅导服务的用户总量
coaching, divided by the total number of users who are enrolled in any course,
除以报名参加任何课程的用户总量
all within a one-week period.
你仅收集一周时间内的这些数据
And you're diverting based on user ID.
你根据用户 ID 进行分组
In each case, check the box if you think the analytical and
请勾选出你认为分析方差和经验方差
the empirical variance would match.
可能一致的案例